(Amy:)And I was distracted.
(Amy:)He has on
extra baby powder today.
(Sheldon:)Is he okay?
(Penny:)He's still in surgery.
(exhales)
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Penny:)He's gonna be all right.
(Penny:)That is sticky.
(Amy:)Come on,
let's talk about something
(Amy:)other than the surgery.
(Sheldon:)That's a good idea.
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)Penny, did you and Leonard ever
discuss funeral arrangements?
(Penny:)I think she meant
something a little happier.
(Sheldon:)I suppose we could try
to make it a celebration,
(Sheldon:)but he died so young.
(knocking on door)
(Howard:)Knock, knock.
Hi.
Hey.
(Raj:)What brings you by?
(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Bernadette:)muffin much.
(Howard:)Told you-- not funny.
(Bernadette:)He's just not laughing
(Bernadette:)because he's feeling...
blue berry.